let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "which of followings is not the process of water cycle?",
    answer: "Decomposition",
    options: [
      "Precipitation",
      "Condensation",
      "Decomposition",
      "Surface water flow"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "When clouds get too heavy to hold water in the water cycle, what happens?",
    answer: "The water falls to the Earth",
    options: [
      "The water falls to the Earth",
      "The water evaporates",
      "Another cloud forms",
      "The clouds get very large"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What turns water on the Earth into vapor in the water cycle?",
    answer: "The sun",
    options: [
      "Global warming",
      "The sun",
      "Water treatment centers",
      "The moon"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In the water cycle what is it called when water goes up through a plant and is turned into a vapor?",
    answer: "Evaporation",
    options: [
      "Precipitation",
      "Evaporation",
      "Condensation",
      "Sublemation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which stage is NOT part of the water cycle?",
    answer: "Emancipation",
    options: [
      "Evaporation",
      "Precipitation",
      "Condensation",
      "Emancipation"
    ]
  },
    {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Condensation is when warm vapor rises, gets cold and does what In the water cycle?",
     answer: "Gathers in clouds",
     options: [
       "Gathers in clouds",
       "Warms up again",
       "Keeps rising until it turns to ice",
       "Falls out of the sky"
     ]
   },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What percentage of the total electro power of Tajikistan is generated by Hydro electro stations?",
    answer: "Almost 90%",
     options: [
       "5%",
       "Almost 90%",
       "Almost 10%",
       "Almost 100%"
     ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What percentage of the total area of Tajikistan is covered by graciers?",
    answer: "6%",
     options: [
       "5%",
       "6%",
       "0.5%",
       "15%"
     ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In the water cycle, how does water return to the ground?",
    answer: "Precipitation",
     options: [
       "Condensation",
       "Evaporation",
       "Precipitation",
       "Sublimation"
     ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In the water cycle, what happens to water after it evaporates from the ocean?",
    answer: "It condenses into clouds",
     options: [
       "It rains onto the land",
       "It is absorbed by plants",
       "It continues to evaporate into outer space",
       "It condenses into clouds"
     ]
  },
];